inspiredopinions.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Schlesinger Associates, has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy when interacting with Schlesinger Associates in connection with engaging in survey research and when visiting our InspiredOpinions web site (the "Site"). This document will outline how we gather and utilize various sources of information obtained during your visit to the Site. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected at this Site.  **This policy may be updated from time to time without prior notice, so please check back periodically. If you continue to visit our Site and use the services made available to you after such changes have been made, you hereby provide your consent to the changes.** By using or accessing the Site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy.  **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE.**

### Privacy and data protection

In order to fulfil our Mission Statement to Protect Consumer, Health Information and Business Information Privacy, Schlesinger Associates companies adhere to the following policies:

1\. All PII obtained shall be lawfully collected, compiled, stored, allowed access to, processed and utilized by Schlesinger Associates companies.   
2\. Participation in all research projects is voluntary and respondents may opt out of any research project, at any time. In addition, consent will be obtained prior to the collection of PII that will be recorded.   
3\. All PII obtained shall be treated confidentially, shall be used for research purposes only and shall not be disclosed to any person not employed by Schlesinger Associates companies, except with consent, as required by law or by court order.   
4\. All PII obtained shall not be disclosed to any client other than for lawful research purposes. In this regard, in general, clients will not receive (a) the last name or telephone number of any recruited Respondent for any research study; (b) any original screeners or sign-out sheets containing any last names or telephone numbers. Further, clients are bound by Schlesinger's Privacy Policy and any such information shared with clients will be used for marketing research and opinion research purposes only.   
5\. Schlesinger Associates companies adhere to the policy laws of all countries in which we manage research.   
6\. Schlesinger Associates companies will not transfer personal data to a country or territory outside the U.S. or the European Economic Area unless that territory or country ensures an adequate level of protection for the rights and freedoms of data subjects.   
7\. Schlesinger Associates companies adhere to research industry Codes and Standards relating to the USA and additionally the country in which each Schlesinger Associates company is based.

**Personal and Non-Personal Information Collected:**

When using the Site, in order to utilize some of the services, you may be asked to provide, or you may choose to upload, certain personally identifiable information about yourself ("Personal Information"). Personal Information can include your email address, physical address, and telephone number. Please note that Personal Information may also include personally identifiable information you voluntarily provide when you take a survey.

In addition, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as IP host address, pages viewed, browser type and other data, and may aggregate any Personal Information collected, such as demographic information, in a manner which does not identify any one person ("Aggregate Information"). Survey answers that are not connected to Personal Information may also constitute Aggregate Information.

Information obtained in connection with the Site may be intermingled with and used by us in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than the Site, including both offline and online sources.

**Information Usage:**

We may use the Personal Information we collect to contact you about our products and services or those of our partners or other third parties from time to time. We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties or mass marketers. We may share your Personal Information with our affiliates, technical consultants, third party auditors or other third parties, who compile the Aggregate Information, make our Site available, enhance its functionality or provide associated services and/or who process your orders and/or deliver content, samples, products, services, gifts and prizes.

We may use your Aggregate Information to do such things as operate our Site, enhance our Site, and for our market research purposes. We may share Aggregate Information with our business partners, clients and other third parties for advertising, promotional and other purposes. Individual answers to questions from you may be shared with our business partners, but those answers will not be labeled with, or linked to, your Personal Information.

Please note that we reserve the right to and may disclose Personal Information about you in response to (a) requests from local, state or federal law enforcement officials; (b) any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding or order, such as subpoena; (c) if required by law; or (d) to investigate suspected fraud, harassment, physical threats, or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, the Site rules or policies, or the rights of third parties or to investigate any suspected conduct which we deem improper. Please also note that we do reserve the right to transfer your personally identifiable information and other information to our successors in business and purchasers of site assets.

**Protection for Children:**

We have no intention of collecting personal information directly from children under the age of 18. When we become aware that personal information from a child under 18 has been collected without such child's parent or guardian's consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**Protection for Health and Financial Information:**

Schlesinger Associates respects your privacy and will use best efforts to maintain the confidentiality of any personal health or financial information that you may provide to us. We will only use such personal health or financial information in the manner and to the extent we use any other Personal Information that you may provide to us, as detailed in this privacy policy. Only certain individuals at Schlesinger Associates will ever have access to your personal health and/or financial information. We will at all times limit the disclosure of your personal health and/or financial information to the minimum number of individuals as possible.

If at any time you wish to modify or remove any such Personal Information from our database, or have any concerns with respect to the protection of your Personal Information, please [contact us](https://schlesingerassociates.zendesk.com/hc/en-us).

**Security:**

Schlesinger Associates will not be liable for disclosures of your Personal Information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. We are committed to using commercially reasonable efforts to maintaining the security of your Personal Information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put into place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard and secure the information we collect, including an industry-standard firewall security system. Though we have undertaken all commercially reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized Internet access to data retained in our servers, however, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, no transmission via the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of this and other factors beyond our control, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you transmit to or through our Site. Therefore, by using this Site, you assume all risks associated with any data transmission, including the risk that your Personal Information may be intercepted in transit.

**Policy Modifications:**

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. However, if at any time in the future we plan to use Personal Information in a way that differs from this policy, we will post such changes here. Your continued use of the Service following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. Please check this page periodically for changes to this Privacy Policy.

**Other Web Sites:**

Our Site may contain links to other web sites not owned or maintained by Schlesinger Associates. Other web sites may also reference or link to our Site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site, or surf the Internet, and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that you visit. We do not endorse, screen or approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites.

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**

This Site may use "cookies" to improve our service. A cookie is a small data file that web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie file can contain various types of information, including a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. We may use cookies to enhance your experience on this Site, to determine user traffic patterns, and for other similar purposes. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, you can configure your browser to alert you when a web site is attempting to send you a cookie and at that time you will have the option of refusing the cookie in which case you may still use the Site, but it may interfere with some of its functionality.

As noted above, we may supplement the information we receive on this Site with information from third party sources. As an example, we may combine cookie data gathered on this Site with cookie data from a third party in order to improve our services. For instance, in some surveys, a third party website may look for cookies on your browser. If the third party detects the cookies, it may gather information about where you have seen a particular ad and how many times you have seen it. No personally identifiable information, such as your email address, would be transmitted via this cookie; however, this third party information would still enhance our ability to compile useful data from the survey.

We may use third-party advertising companies to measure advertising effectiveness. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons). Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. This anonymous information does not include your address, email address, or other personally identifiable information. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site (as discussed above), cookies received with banner ads are collected by those advertisers and their ad service providers, and we do not have access to that information. The ad company's privacy policy and/or that of its service provider will govern the use of this information and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such ad company.

**Clickstream:**

As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as "clickstream data," may be collected and stored by a web site's server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of computer and browsing software you use and the address of the web site from which you linked to the Site. We may collect and use clickstream data as a form of Aggregate Information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of our Site, how visitors navigate throughout the Site and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors. This information will be used to improve our Site and our services. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregate, and will not contain any Personal Information.

**Site Terms and Conditions:**

Use of this Site is governed by the provisions contained in the Terms and Conditions. Your use, or access, of the Site constitutes your agreement to be bound by these provisions.  **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITE.**

**Contact:**

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, you may contact us by email at [help@inspiredopinions.com](mailto:help@inspiredopinions.com), or by mail at InspiredOpinions, Privacy Inquiries, 101 Wood Avenue South, Suite 501, Iselin, NJ 08830.

Phone number: +1 (855) 244-0886

**United States of America:**  Our Site is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Site, you authorize the export of Personal Information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy. If you are not a U.S. citizen, you expressly consent to the processing of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, even if the laws in your country may be more stringent with respect to the processing of personally identifiable

The terms of this Privacy Policy are effective and were last updated on September 11, 2012.
